Perls Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Photographs, circa 1937-1995, Series 3:; (Boxes 60-75, OV 84; 16.1 linear feet)
  - Inventory, circa 1937-1995, 3.2
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 7027-7267, 1912-1918 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 9125-9967, 1913-1917, (see also Box 80, Folder 6) (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 10190-10906, 1912-1918 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 11066-11984, 1911-1919 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 12006-12538, 1910-1919 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 12695-12840, 1912-1919 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 12949-12982, 1911-1918 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13052-13372, 1912-1918 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13373, 1915, 1989-1991 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13376-13378, 1908-1910 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13422-13479, 1910-1918 (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13523-13613, 1913-1918 (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13736-13794, 1918 (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13800-13850, 1910-1916 (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13855-13858, 1916-1919 (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 13860-13973, 1912-1918 (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, Consignment, 1918, 1929, 1949-1950, 1971-1972, 1988-1989 (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, Elaine Ganz, 1916-1917 (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, Returned January 1992, 13959, 1918 (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Pascin, Jules, Oils, 6153-13399, 1914-1924 (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Pascin, Jules, Oils, 13656-13766, 1917-1929 (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Pascin, Jules, Oils, 13796-13847, 1909-1929 (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Pascin, Jules, Drawings, 13682-13848, 1906-1928 (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Pascin, Jules, Drawings, 5764-5913, 1908-1930 (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Pascin, Jules, Drawings, 6047-9851, 1907-1926 (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Pascin, Jules, Drawings, 10895-12796, 1905-1920 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Pascin, Jules, Drawings, 12810-13093, 1912-1929 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Pascin, Jules, P2540-4577, 1905-1929 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Pascin, Jules, 3187-5226, 1917-1925 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Pascin, Jules, 5528-5778, 1917-1928 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Pascin, Jules, 5828-5981, 1903-1930 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Pascin, Jules, 6029-6198, 1903-1926 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Pascin, Jules, 6201-6415, 1907-1928 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Pascin, Jules, 6431-6597, 1915-1927 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Pascin, Jules, 6634-10379, 1905-1929 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Pascin, Jules, 11038-11215, 1918-1926 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Pascin, Jules, 11467-13740, 1900-1928 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Pascin, Jules, 9120-9732, 1914-1925 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Pascin, Jules, 9809-10905, 1908-1928 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Pascin, Jules, 12733-12831, 1907-1930 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Pascin, Jules, 12846-12919, 1907-1928 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Pascin, Jules, 12922-13086, 1916-1929 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Pascin, Jules, 13094-13334, 1912-1929 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Pascin, Jules, 13354-13398, 1912-1930 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Pascin, Jules, 13400-13442, 1917-1928 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Pascin, Jules, 13443-13626, 1914-1929 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Pascin, Jules, 13628-13676, 1916-1929 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Pascin, Jules, 13712-13795, 1922-1929 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Peyronnet, Dominique, 13669, circa 1910-1943 (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 24-4811, 1906-1944 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 5016-5658, 1900-1948 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 5664-5976, 1903-1956 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6013-6088, 1953-1956 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6109-6271, 1903-1959 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6272-6394, 1921-1957 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6411-6677, 1917-1959 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6702-6760, 1913-1959 (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6803-6892, 1922-1965 (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 6900-6977, 1907-1965 (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 7009-9864, 1908-1969 (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 10065-10890, 1904-1969 (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 11223-12750, 1915-1963 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 12754-12881, 1901-1970 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 12926-12995, 1908-1970 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13009-13099, 1906-1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13100-13250, 1924-1969 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13302-13381, 1932-1962 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13385-13534, 1904-1968 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13553-13571, 1937-1955 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13732-13753, 1922-1954 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 13814-13974, 1932 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Picasso, Pablo, P24-P6342, circa 1920-1923 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Rimbert, Réné, 1578-11474, 1955-1967 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Rimbert, Réné, 11475-13129, 1952-1971 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Rouault, Georges, 304-4841, 1913-1939 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Rouault, Georges, 5023-5295, 1905-1938 (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Rouault, Georges, 5327-5857, 1909-1938 (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Rouault, Georges, 6079-6386, 1906-1952 (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Rouault, Georges, 6544-6888, 1905-1953 (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Rouault, Georges, 7005-9909, 1905-1956 (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Rouault, Georges, 10297-11793, 1925-1956 (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Rouault, Georges, 12604-12939, 1905-1937 (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Rouault, Georges, 13203-13604, 1918-1937 (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Rouault, Georges, P37-P7286, circa 1908 (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Rouault, Georges, Not Our Negatives, 1908-1954 (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Rouault, Georges, Not Our Negatives, 1929-1956 (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 3040-5495, 1919-1928 (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 5727-6708, 1920-1939 (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 6806-9719, 1917-1928 (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 10702-11468, 1920-1942 (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 11704-12338, 1921-1927 (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 12736-12889, 1920-1928 (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Soutine, Chaim, 13112-13982, 1918-1939 (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Soutine, Chaim, P2415-P5530, circa 1920 (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 3540-9545, 1946-1968 (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 10022-10114, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 10350-10359, 1970-1971 (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 10360-10551, 1927-1971 (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 10721-10763, 1938-1972 (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 10814-10877, 1945-1973 (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 10878-10883, 1972-1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 11140-11917, 1942-1973 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, 12026-13361, 1932-1971 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Tamayo, Rufino, P6737, 1920 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 564-5954, 1910-1952 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 6146-6854, 1910-1949 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 9321-10885, 1910-1912 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 12650-13295, 1919-1939 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, 13317-13653, 1909-1948 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Utrillo, Maurice, P1385-P6868, 1912 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Van Dongen, Kees, 5608-12791, 1905-1938 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Van Dongen, Kees, 13008-13977, 1906-1925 (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Vivin, Louis, 4658-6988, 1925-1935 (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Vivin, Louis, 7018-7150, 1930-1935 (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Vivin, Louis, 9059-9885, 1910-1935 (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Vivin, Louis, 11398-12980, 1925-1930 (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Vivin, Louis, 13005-13864, 1910-1935 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - Vivin, Louis, P4517, 1925 (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 872-5979, 1906-1952 (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 6055-6595, 1906-1952 (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 6657-6979, 1905-1948 (Box 73, Folder 21)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 7044-7333, 1903-1950 (Box 73, Folder 22)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 9290-9982, 1904-1928 (Box 73, Folder 23)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 10442-12953, 1904-1950 (Box 73, Folder 24)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, 13296-13863, 1905-1912 (Box 73, Folder 25)
    - Vlaminck, Maurice de, P49-P49667, 1905 (Box 73, Folder 26)
    - African, 4626-5728, 1880-1952 (Box 73, Folder 27)
    - African, 5816-9848, 18th century (Box 73, Folder 28)
    - African, 10461-11299, 18th century, circa 1900 (Box 73, Folder 29)
    - African, 11302-11318, undated (Box 73, Folder 30)
    - African, 11319-11329, undated (Box 73, Folder 31)
    - African, 11333-11339, undated (Box 73, Folder 32)
    - African, 11340-11351, undated (Box 73, Folder 33)
    - African, 11362-11379, undated (Box 73, Folder 34)
    - African, 11384-11389, undated (Box 73, Folder 35)
    - African, 11390-11400, undated (Box 73, Folder 36)
    - African, 11401-11411, 17th century (Box 73, Folder 37)
    - African, 11412-11443, undated (Box 73, Folder 38)
    - African, 11444-11448, undated (Box 73, Folder 39)
    - African, 11449-11481, undated (Box 73, Folder 40)
    - African, 11741-12172, 19th century (Box 73, Folder 41)
    - African, P6203-P10109, 18th - 19th century, 1900-1980 (Box 73, Folder 42)
    - Assyrian, P9263-P10106A, 10414, 900 BC (Box 73, Folder 43)
    - Benin, P1295-P7811, 17th - 19th century (Box 73, Folder 44)
    - Benin, P7885-P9199, 17th - 19th century (Box 73, Folder 45)
    - Benin, P9200-P9495, 17th - 19th century (Box 73, Folder 46)
    - Benin, P9521-P9744, 17th - 19th century (Box 73, Folder 47)
    - Benin, P9745-P9835, 18th - 19th century (Box 73, Folder 48)
    - Benin, P9837-P9939, 18th - 19th century, 1990 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Benin, P9940-P9977, 17th - 18th century (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Benin, P9981-P10037, 17th - 19th century (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Benin, P10096-P10132, undated (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Benin, Not Our Negatives, 1988, undated (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Benin, Installations and Slides, 17th - 19th century, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Egyptian, P4352-P9784, 1320 BC - 600 BC (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Egyptian, P9820-P9983, 2000 BC - 600 BC (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Egyptian, Sold, 300 BC (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Etruscan, P9767-P9844, 500 BC - 300 BC (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Far East, P5622-P9997, 11th - 19th century (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Greek, P9678-P9813, 400 BC - 100 BC (Box 74, Folder 12)
    - Indian, P4522-P10108, circa 1000-1850 (Box 74, Folder 13)
    - Indonesian/Sumatran, P8204-P10119, circa 1900 (Box 74, Folder 14)
    - Japanese, P8562-P9424, 17th - 19th century (Box 74, Folder 15)
    - New Ireland, Guinea, Maori, Solomon, Easter Island, Polynesia, P2247-P7826, 18th - 20th century (Box 74, Folder 16)
    - New Ireland, Guinea, Maori, Solomon, Easter Island, Polynesia, P7840-P9943, 1880-1900 (Box 74, Folder 17)
    - North American, Eskimo, Pacific Coast, P7519-P9480, 19th century (Box 74, Folder 18)
    - Pre-Columbian, P2101-P6200, 300 AD - 1200 AD (Box 74, Folder 19)
    - Pre-Columbian, P7917-P8129, 500 AD - 800 AD (Box 74, Folder 20)
    - Pre-Columbian, P9143-P10131, circa 500 AD - 950 AD, 1967, 1981-1991 (Box 74, Folder 21)
    - Roman Empire/Asia Minor, P9416-P9609, circa 100 AD (Box 74, Folder 22)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 1958, (see also Box 70, Folder 17) (Box 80 (sol), Folder 5)
  - Artist Files, circa 1937-1995, 3.3
    Filed here are photographs depicting artwork by artists not represented by the gallery. Most of these photographs do not bear photograph or stock numbers.
    The photographs are arranged alphabetically by artist, collector, or theme according to their original folder headings.
    - African Sculptures, 4903-5507, undated (Box 74, Folder 23)
    - Avery, Milton, 12319-12321, undated (Box 74, Folder 24)
    - Balthus, unnumbered, 1937 (Box 74, Folder 25)
    - Baum, Mark, 1361-1363, undated (Box 74, Folder 26)
    - Blanchard, Carol, 738-4031, 1944-1952 (Box 74, Folder 27)
    - Bluestein, 7166-7183, 1885-1955 (Box 74, Folder 28)
    - Bonnard, Pierre, 3368, unnumbered, 1914 (Box 74, Folder 29)
    - Brauner, Victor, 5466, unnumbered, undated (Box 74, Folder 30)
    - Campigli, Massimo, unnumbered, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 31)
    - Cantú, Federico, 1257-1259, unnumbered, undated (Box 74, Folder 32)
    - Carreño, Mario, 1262-1665, undated (Box 74, Folder 33)
    - Carreño, Mario, 2152-2772, circa 1946 (Box 74, Folder 34)
    - Carreño, Mario, 2965-3941, circa 1950 (Box 74, Folder 35)
    - Carreño, Mario, unnumbered, circa 1946 (Box 74, Folder 36)
    - Cassatt, Mary, unnumbered, circa 1915 (Box 74, Folder 37)
    - Cezanne, Paul, unnumbered, circa 1948 (Box 74, Folder 38)
    - Chirico, Giorgio de, 327-18, circa 1927-1981 (Box 74, Folder 39)
    - Cocteau, Jean, unnumbered, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 40)
    - Corcos, Lucille, unnumbered, undated (Box 74, Folder 41)
    - Corinth, Lovis, unnumbered, 1928, 1945 (Box 74, Folder 42)
    - Courbet, Gustave, unnumbered, 1871 (Box 74, Folder 43)
    - Cross, Henri, 7179, undated (Box 74, Folder 44)
    - Czobel, Bela, P2789, undated (Box 74, Folder 45)
    - Day, Esther Worden, 1359-1375, unnumbered, undated (Box 74, Folder 46)
    - Degas, Edgar, 560-813, unnumbered, undated (Box 74, Folder 47)
    - De Groot Collection, P2418-P2433, 1848-1929 (Box 74, Folder 48)
    - Fresnaye, Roger de la, 3232, unnumbered, circa 1911 (Box 74, Folder 49)
    - de Kooning, Willem, 10776, 1964 (Box 74, Folder 50)
    - Di Cosimo, Piero, unnumbered, undated (Box 74, Folder 51)
    - Dufresne, Charles, 6745, unnumbered, circa 1929 (Box 74, Folder 52)
    - Dufy, Jean, 214-218, unnumbered, circa 1939-1957 (Box 74, Folder 53)
    - Edzard, Dietz, 3307, unnumbered, circa 1956 (Box 74, Folder 54)
    - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 3258-3581, 1947-1948 (Box 74, Folder 55)
    - Eisendieck, Suzanne, 3647-5062, 1938-1951 (Box 74, Folder 56)
    - Eisendieck, Suzanne, unnumbered, 1940-1950 (Box 74, Folder 57)
    - Enson, James, 5213, unnumbered, 1926-1930 (Box 74, Folder 58)
    - Eve, Jean, 188-4934, 1930-1946 (Box 74, Folder 59)
    - Eve, Jean, 4935-5175, 1941-1952 (Box 74, Folder 60)
    - Eve, Jean, 5177-5333, 1929-1953 (Box 74, Folder 61)
    - Eve, Jean, 5342-5488, 1950-1954 (Box 74, Folder 62)
    - Eve, Jean, 5537-12175, 1930-1956 (Box 74, Folder 63)
    - Eve, Jean, unnumbered, 1930-1958 (Box 74, Folder 64)
    - Fantin-Latour, Henri, unnumbered, 1858 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Faurec, Urbain, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Fein, Sylvia, 880-2702, undated (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Forain, Jean Louis, 887-3339, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - French, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Friesz, E. Othon, 521-5133, 1905-1909 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Friedman, Martin, 2065-2349, undated (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Galván, Guerrero, 1275-1709, unnumbered, circa 1950 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Gauguin, Paul, unnumbered, circa 1894 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Gérard, Rolf, unnumbered, 1937 (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - Giacometti, Alberto, 12325, unnumbered, 1950-1960 (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Glasco, Joseph, 3842-5467, circa 1949 (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Gleizes, Albert, 5539-5540, 1916 (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Gromaire, Marcel, 3721, undated (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - Haucke, Frederick, 890-2792, undated (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Cherry Jeffe, Huldah, 2262, undated (Box 75, Folder 16)
    - Izquierdo, maria, 1206, undated (Box 75, Folder 17)
    - Jacob, Max, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 18)
    - John, Augustus, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 19)
    - Kandinsky, Wassily, 6941, undated, 1903-1929 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    - Kisling, Moise, 5392-11563, 1926-1938 (Box 75, Folder 21)
    - Klee, Paul, 4608-10417, 1914-1939 (Box 75, Folder 22)
    - Lam, Wifredo, 495-499, undated (Box 75, Folder 23)
    - La More, Chet, 1825-2663, 1942-1946 (Box 75, Folder 24)
    - Laurencin, Marie, 105-6364, unnumbered, 1912-1925 (Box 75, Folder 25)
    - Legrand, Louis, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 26)
    - Lloyd, Otho, 251-266, circa 1933 (Box 75, Folder 27)
    - Maclet, Elisée, 1220-1227, undated (Box 75, Folder 28)
    - Manet, Edouard, 1142, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 29)
    - Marquet, Albert, 5855, unnumbered, 1944-1952 (Box 75, Folder 30)
    - Martinez-Pedro, Luis, 2090-37963, unnumbered, 1944-1949 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    - Masereel, Frans, 450-467, unnumbered, 1927-1939 (Box 75, Folder 32)
    - Masson, André, 12328-12329, circa 1957 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Masterller, John, 2325-2945, 1945-1947 (Box 75, Folder 34)
    - Matta, Roberto, 6284-6292, 1957-1959 (Box 75, Folder 35)
    - Metzinger, Jean, 485, undated (Box 75, Folder 36)
    - Meza, Guillermo, 1211, undated (Box 75, Folder 37)
    - Monet, Claude, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 38)
    - Montenegro, Roberto, 1213-3444, undated (Box 75, Folder 39)
    - Monticelli, Adolphe, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 40)
    - Munch, Edvard, unnumbered, 1912-1913, 1993 (Box 75, Folder 41)
    - Nichols, John, unnumbered, circa 1937 (Box 75, Folder 42)
    - Orozco, José Clemente, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 43)
    - Papsdorf, Fred, 759-1955, 1935-1946 (Box 75, Folder 44)
    - Papsdorf, Fred, 2011-3723, 1944-1947 (Box 75, Folder 45)
    - Papsdorf, Fred, unnumbered, 1944-1947 (Box 75, Folder 46)
    - Pencz, Georg, 7288, unnumbered, 1544, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 47)
    - Pereny, Madelaine, 790-1922, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 48)
    - Peyronnet, Dominique, 6525, unnumbered, 1930-1941 (Box 75, Folder 49)
    - Pignon, Edouard, 5982-6066, 1949-1957 (Box 75, Folder 50)
    - Pissarro, Camille, unnumbered, 1901 (Box 75, Folder 51)
    - Pompon, François, 6649-6683, 1908-1920 (Box 75, Folder 52)
    - Priebe, Karl, 696-2936, 1942-1947 (Box 75, Folder 53)
    - Priebe, Karl, 2941-3786, 1947-1949 (Box 75, Folder 54)
    - Priebe, Karl, 3801-3836, unnumbered, 1946-1949 (Box 75, Folder 55)
    - Redon, Odilon, 884, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 56)
    - Renoir, Pierre Auguste, 1509, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 57)
    - Rivera, Diego, 1204, unnumbered, circa 1914 (Box 75, Folder 58)
    - Rousseau, Henri, 4812, unnumbered, 1895-1956 (Box 75, Folder 59)
    - Ruysdael, Solomon von, unnumbered, 1644, 1936 (Box 75, Folder 60)
    - Ruiz, Antonio, 1214, 1938 (Box 75, Folder 61)
    - Sacharoff, Olga, 268-281, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 62)
    - Schary, Saul, 733-1606, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 63)
    - Segonzac, André Dunoyer de, 3229-5238, circa 1927 (Box 75, Folder 64)
    - Séraphine, Louis de Senlis, 4781-11178, unnumbered, 1914-1920, 1951-1967 (Box 75, Folder 65)
    - Siquieros, David Alfaro, 1215, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 66)
    - Sisley, Alfred, unnumbered, 19th century (Box 75, Folder 67)
    - Stark, Margaret, 1694-2427, unnumbered, 1944-1945 (Box 75, Folder 68)
    - Stravinsky, Theodore, 529-551, unnumbered, 1934-1953 (Box 75, Folder 69)
    - Strigel, Bernhard, unnumbered, 1929-1931 (Box 75, Folder 70)
    - Takis, Nocholas, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 71)
    - Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri, 3126-3172, unnumbered, 1951, undated (Box 75, Folder 72)
    - Tschabasov, Nahum, 1963-2416, 1944-1946 (Box 75, Folder 73)
    - Tschabasov, Nahum, 2703-3727, unnumbered, 1936-1948 (Box 75, Folder 74)
    - Valadon, Suzanne, 6384-6439, unnumbered, 1923-1929 (Box 75, Folder 75)
    - Van Gogh, Vincent, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 76)
    - Vedovelli, Antonio, 1942-3080, undated (Box 75, Folder 77)
    - Von Ripper, Rudolphe C., 2054, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 78)
    - Vuillard, Edouard, 4825, unnumbered, circa 1902 (Box 75, Folder 79)
    - Wilson, Reginald, 1471-1512, undated (Box 75, Folder 80)
    - Winterhalter, Franz Xavier, unnumbered, undated (Box 75, Folder 81)
    - Zak, Eugène, 5350, 1924 (Box 75, Folder 82)
    - Unidentified, P7-P45, undated (Box 75, Folder 83)
- Exhibition, Loan, and Sales Records, 1937-1995, Series 4:; (Boxes 76-78; 2.1 linear feet)
  There is a relatively amount of records relating to exhibitions, loans, and sales. Found are exhibition lists, schedules, invitations and announcements, photographs of exhibition installations, press releases, and records of loans to other institutions and galleries. Sales records include artist lists, inventory lists, invoices, pick up and delivery receipts, and price lists.
  The Exhibition, Loan, and Sales Records series is arranged by record type into three subseries:
  Subseries 1: Exhibition Records, 1937-1994
  Subseries 2: Loan Records, 1964-1995
  Subseries 3: Sales Records, 1937-1994
  - Exhibition Records, 1937-1994, 4.1
    The exhibition records include attendance records, lists of artwork, price lists, schedules, nvitations and announcements, photographs, press releases, and publicity materials. Exhibition catalogs can be found in Series 6. The folder of photographs of the Aristide Maillol exhibitition in 1970 also includes photographs of Maillol's model, Dina Vierny, posing with sculptures of her.
    - Attendance Books, 1959-1968 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1986-1994 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1981-1985 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Lists, 1965-1980 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1937-1993 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Invitations and Announcements, 1958, 1971-1984 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Invitations, Announcements, and Catalogs from Other Galleries, 1945-1948, 1964-1965, 1970, 1978, 1985, 1992-1993, undated (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, Eisendieck Show, November 1-27, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, Karl Priebe, October 3-29, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, Modigliani and African Sculpture, April 23 - May 19, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, Pablo Picasso "The 1930's," January 5 - February 7, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, Raoul Dufy "20 Masterworks," September 28 - October 31, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, Soutine Exhibition, November 2 - December 5, 1953 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, Cubism to 1918, January 4 - February 6, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, Archipenko, September 29 - October 24, 1959 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, Calder 1960, March 15 - April 9, 1960 (Box 76, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, Calder-Miró Exhibition, February 21 - April 1, 1961 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, Modigliani Show, October 29 - December 7, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, The Nudes of Modigliani, October 11 - November 12, 1966 (Box 76, Folder 19)
    - Photographs, Vlaminck Fauve, April 9 - May 11, 1968 (Box 76, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, Léger ShowNovember 11, 1968 - January 12, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, "Femmes et Filles" Bombois Show, March 4 - April 5, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, 24 Major Acquisitions, April 8 - May 17, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, Chaim Soutine Exhibition, November 11 - December 13, 1969 (Box 76, Folder 24)
    - Photographs, Maillol: Bronzes and Drawings, March 18 - April 18, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, 24 Major Acquisitions, April 21 - May 30, 1970 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, Group Exhibition, January 1971 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Photographs, Alexander Calder Animobiles and Recent Gouaches, October 5 - November 6, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Photographs, Tamayo Oils, November 9 - December 11, 1971 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, Alexander Calder Oil Paintings, October 10 - November 11, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Photographs, Modigliani Exhibition, November 14 - December 16, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Photographs, Alexander Crags and Critters, October 15 - November 16, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 32)